Guide to the Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Audiovisual Materials, 1956-2018 RL.10006_AV RL.10006_AV
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 1974-2017; 347 items
  - Audio interviews, 1974-2001; 189 items
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:15 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0023_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616214)
    - Larry Rivers, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1977; 00:42:02 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0061_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615985)
    - Larry Rivers, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:42:58 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0061_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615983)
    - James Rosenquist, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:31:12 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0276_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615912)
    - David Ross, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:24 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0034_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616187)
    - David Ross, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:25:10 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0034_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616189)
    - David Ross, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:25 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0035_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616190)
    - David Ross, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:20 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0035_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616192)
    - Robert Ryman, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:28 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0009_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616219)
    - Robert Ryman, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:43 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0009_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616217)
    - Robert Ryman, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1992; 00:47:14 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0155_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615877)
    - Robert Ryman, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1992; 00:29:48 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0155_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615880)
    - David Salle, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:14 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0046_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616184)
    - David Salle, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:20 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0046_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616182)
    - David Salle, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:15 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0047_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616223)
    - David Salle, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:18:17 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0047_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616222)
    - Mary Ann Scherr, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:31:37 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0192_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615902)
    - Mary Ann Scherr, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:31:38 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0192_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615901)
    - Gerald Schoenfeld, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:47:17 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0275_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615908)
    - Gerald Schoenfeld, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:47:18 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0275_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615907)
    - Richard Serra, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 01:02:28 (Box Unknown, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0015_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616168)
    - Richard Serra, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:28:50 (Box Unknown, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0015_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616167)
    - Mary Shaffer, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:31:24 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0066_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615953)
    - Mary Shaffer, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:31:29 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0066_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615955)
    - Mary Shaffer, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:17:33 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0067_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616008)
    - Joel Shapiro, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:16 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0020_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616237)
    - Joel Shapiro, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:19 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0020_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616235)
    - Joel Shapiro, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:34:55 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0021_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616183)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:04 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0025_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615970)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:03 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0025_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615968)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:34:31 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0026_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616090)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:34:31 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0043_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616020)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:35 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0044_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615944)
    - Beverly Sills, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:40 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0044_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615946)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:17 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0027_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615903)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:19 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0027_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615900)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:31:58 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0028_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616079)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:31:49 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0029_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616019)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:24 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0030_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615974)
    - Ruth Simmons, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:12 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0030_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615973)
    - Siskind, Aaron, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1981; 00:39:37 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0051_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616152)
    - Siskind, Aaron, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1981; 01:01:59 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0051_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616154)
    - Siskind, Aaron, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:09:07 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0193_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616044)
    - Sister Parish, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 01:00:39 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0184_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616082)
    - Holly Solomon, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 01:02:50 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0013_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616225)
    - Laurinda Spear, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:26 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0085_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616034)
    - Laurinda Spear, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:24 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0085_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616032)
    - Laurinda Spear, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:29 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0086_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615932)
    - Laurinda Spear, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:23:17 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0086_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615934)
    - Carl Spielvogel, Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 2001; 00:31:01 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0238_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616063)
    - Gloria Steinem, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:13 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0001_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615933)
    - Gloria Steinem, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:16 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0001_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615935)
    - Gloria Steinem, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:13:08 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0017_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616050)
    - Gloria Steinem, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:15 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0032_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615975)
    - Gloria Steinem, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:11 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0032_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615972)
    - Frank Stella, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1985; 00:30:15 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0180_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616080)
    - William Styron, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:02:38 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0005_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616085)
    - William Styron, James Wolfensohn, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:02:38 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0046_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615897)
    - Studs Terkel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1974; 00:31:49 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0226_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616048)
    - Studs Terkel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1974; 00:31:43 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0226_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616046)
    - Studs Terkel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1974; 00:31:38 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0229_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615887)
    - Studs Terkel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1974; 00:10:29 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0229_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615886)
    - Twyla Tharp, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:15 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0019_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616015)
    - Twyla Tharp, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:17 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0019_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616014)
    - Twyla Tharp, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:12 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0049_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616069)
    - Twyla Tharp, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:46:56 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0049_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616067)
    - Twyla Tharp, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:01:50 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0050_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615895)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, Margaret Truman, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:03:51 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0284_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616076)
    - Kirk Varnedoe, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:27 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0038_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616175)
    - Kirk Varnedoe, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:17 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0038_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616173)
    - Kirk Varnedoe, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:05:41 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0039_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616171)
    - Kirk Varnedoe, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:23 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0039_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616169)
    - Joel Wachs, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1992; 00:30:08 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0166_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616088)
    - Joel Wachs, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1992; 00:31:42 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0166_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616086)
    - Lawrence Weiner, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:32:08 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0004_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616240)
    - Lawrence Weiner, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:54 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0004_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616242)
    - Lawrence Weiner, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:33 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0005_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616233)
    - Elie Wiesel, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:46:59 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0004_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615942)
    - Elie Wiesel, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:46:21 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0004_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615940)
    - Elie Wiesel, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:47:13 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0034_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616016)
    - Elie Wiesel, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:46:08 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0034_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616017)
    - Lilyan Wilder, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:32:30 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0240_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615949)
    - Lilyan Wilder, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:16:23 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0240_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615950)
    - James Wolfensohn, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:21 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0045_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615914)
    - James Wolfensohn, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:22 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0045_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615916)
    - James Wolfensohn, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:15 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0003_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616051)
    - James Wolfensohn, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:25 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0003_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616054)
  - Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Visiting Filmmaker Series, 2011-2017; 4 items
    - James Longley, 2010-10-29 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0009)
    - Laura Poitras, 2012-10-24 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0023)
    - Stanley Nelson, 2014-10-17 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0011)
    - Carlos Sandoval, 2017-03-07 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0003)
  - Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, 2014; 2 items
    - Roy Furman, 2014-07-17 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0003)
    - Robert A.M. Stern, 2014-08-14 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0002)
- Historic Preservation Videos, 1978-2018; 69 items Video cassettes and files.
  The Historic Preservation Video, 1978-2018, series documents Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel's extensive involvement in historic preservation.
  - Historic Landmarks Preservation Center Cultural Medallion presentations, 2011-2019; 34 items
    Chronologically by date of recording.
    The Historic Landmarks Preservation Center (HLPC) Cultural Medallion presentation series documents Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel's efforts with HLPC to preserve and recognize residences in New York City occupied by prominent individuals. The programs consist of medallion presentations on location, and include remarks by Diamonstein-Spielvogel and others.
    - Edith Wharton, 2011-10-05; 0:25:14 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0010)
    - Edward Stone, 2012-03-15; 0:18:38 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0009)
    - Odetta, 2012-07-17; 0:55:58 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0005)
    - Richard Wright, 2012-07-17; 0:26:38 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0002)
    - Harry Lloyd Hopkins, 2013-05-06; 0:38:04 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0020)
    - Miles Davis, 2013-05-16; 0:45:01 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0021)
    - Edward Hopper, 2013-09-12; 0:37:59 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0036)
    - Albert Sprague Bard, 2013-09-23; 0:26:57 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0041)
    - Barnett Newman, 2013-10-08; 0:42:58 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0038)
    - Woody Guthrie, 2013-10-16; 0:39:11 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0039)
    - Ada Louise Huxtable, 2013-11-13; 0:23:45 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0042)
    - Ed Koch, 2013-12-12; 0:40:18 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0040)
    - Lincoln Kirstein, 2013-12-12; 0:36:02 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0037)
    - Oscar J. Hijuelos, 2014-04-23; 0:33:41 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0034)
    - Sinclair Lewis, 2014-05-09; 0:35:37 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0035)
    - John Vliet Lindsay, 2014-09-10; 0:57:58 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0001)
    - Bella Abzug, 2014-10-07; 1:02:18 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0016)
    - Jonas Salk, 2015-03-26; 0:40:36 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MOV-0002)
    - Mayor John Purroy Mitchel, 2015-09-29; 0:50:40 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0005)
    - Ethel Waters, 2015-10-21; 0:33:32 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0004)
    - Arthur Miller, 2016-10-17; 0:47:01 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0007)
    - Leonard Bernstein, 2017-05-04; 1:10:01 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0008)
    - Jerome Robbins, 2017-10-10; 0:46:51 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0009)
    - Lorraine Hansberry, 2017-10-16; 0:54:28 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0010)
    - Edith (Edie) Windsor, 2018-04-17; 0:55:40 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0011)
    - Eleanor and Franklin Delano Roosevelt, 2018-04-24; 0:40:56 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0012)
    - Charles Dana Gibson, 2018-04-25; 0:39:14 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0014)
    - Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn, 2018-04-25; 0:43:57 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0013)
    - Wallace Stevens, 2018-07-11; 0:36:15 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0015)
    - Ella Fitzgerald, 2018-08-08; 1:52:36 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0020)
    - Merce Cunningham, 2018-09-20; 0:49:10 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0021)
    - David Dubinsky, 2018-10-25; 0:56:12 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0022)
    - Condé Nast, 2018-11-14; 0:42:14 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0023)
    - Philip Roth, 2019-10-29; 0:53:38 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0009)
  - Historic Preservation Discussions and Programs, 1978-2016; 2; 36 items
    - Straight Talk: Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1978; 0:19:43 (Box 3, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0044)
    - Historic Landmarks, 1990-04-11 (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0192)
    - The P.S. 86K Landmark Gala, 1992-06-10 (Box 67, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0183)
    - New York City Landmarks:WABC-TV New York Views, 1992-06-29 (Box 71, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0224)
    - Best Talk:Landmarks Show, 1994 (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0188)
    - The Landmarks of New York, 1998-03-31 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0263)
    - Landmarks of Chicago and New York: A Tale of Two Cities, 1999 (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0189)
    - Ginsberg, Allen: Plaque Dedication for Designated Cultural Site: Metroview CUNY TV-75, 2000 (Box 74, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0259)
    - High Line Supporters: New York's Elected Officials, 2004 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0019)
    - Jane's New York: On the High Line, 2004 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0030)
    - 45th Anniversary of the Landmarks Law Luncheon, April 19, 2010, 2010-04-19; 1:08:10 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0023)
    - Exhibit images for Landmarks of New York, 2011-04-22 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0045)
    - The Landmarks of New York, 2011-09-19 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0007)
    - The Historic Districts Council Gala in Honor of Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, 2011-10-26 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0001)
    - Eldridge & Co., Interview, 2011; 0:28:59 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0015, 0016)
    - Landmarks of New York V, SUNY Presentation, 2011; 0:21:10 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0007)
    - Landmarks of New York Discussion Series: A Talk By Gillian Tett, 2012-07-05; 1:07:02 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0008)
    - Landmarks of New York Discussion Series: The Highline, 2012-07-26; 1:08:06 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0007)
    - Landmarks of New York Discussion Series: Robert A. M. Stern, 2012-08-09; 0:59:45 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0005)
    - Landmarks of New York Discussion Series: David Rockwell "Untold Stories, 2012-08-23; 1:02:23 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0006)
    - Elizabeth Diller: The Landmarks of Tomorrow, 2012-12-17; 1:18:28 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0011)
    - Diller Scofidio + Renfro:Reimagining Lincoln Center and the High Line, 2012 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0017)
    - An Evening with Robert A.M. Stern and Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, 2013-01-15; 1:00:10 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0022)
    - art21 on the High Line. El Anatsui--"Broken Bridge II", 2013 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0018)
    - art21 on the High Line. Sarah Sze--Broadcast Segment, 2013 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0018)
    - Honor Our Past, Imagine Our Future: Fifty Years of NYC Landmarks Law, 1965-2015, 2015-03-31; 1:32:01 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0043)
    - NYC Landmarks50 Alliance Gala, April 15, 2015, 2015-04-15; 1:38:31 (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0044)
    - Treasures of New York:The Landmarks Preservation Movement, 2015 (Box 759, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0058)
    - NYC Landmarks50 Anniversary Celebration, April 14, 2016, 2016-04-14; 1:17:51 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-MP4-0001)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel receives Georgian Group Preservation Award, 2016-09-14; 0:33:08 (Digital-materials SET-0001, Video-file RL10006-M4V-0006)
    - Empire State and City Hall Buildings Given Landmark Plaques, undated (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0171)
    - Feinstein, Michael and Landmarks Ceremony:WCBS-TV News at 11, undated (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0190)
    - Landmarks Anniversary Pro Bono Campaign, undated (Box 26, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0395)
    - Landmarks Anniversary Pro Bono Campaign, undated (Box 68, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0191)
    - Landmarks of New York, undated (Box 661, Video-disc RL10006-DVD-0026)
    - New York Landmarks, undated (Box 43, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-423)
- Personal and Associated Audiovisual Resources, 1956-2017; 1; 70 items